(Howard:)Well, that and jiggling
her arm fat.
(Leonard:)I can't believe we're going
all the way to San Diego
(Leonard:)to confront this guy.
(Howard:)Yeah, we're kind of
bad-asses, aren't we?
(Raj:)Totally.
(Raj:)Hey, how about
we stay the night
(Raj:)and hit Legoland
in the morning?
(Sheldon:)Sea World is better.
(Sheldon:)It has Shamu, who is
literally tons of fun.
(Sheldon:)But for the moment, let's stay
focused on Todd Zarnecki.
(Raj:)Yeah, we're coming for you,
Todd Zarnecki.
(Raj:)And for the record, Legoland
is more interactive.
(Sheldon:)I almost feel sorry
(Sheldon:)for the poor fool, sitting in
his split-level suburban ranch,
(Sheldon:)unaware that
a vengeful horde is barreling
down the San Diego Freeway
(Sheldon:)at 71 miles an hour.
(Sheldon:)Ease up there, lead foot.
(Sheldon:)You trying to get us killed?
(Raj:)I took the liberty
of burning us
(Raj:)a mix of heroic
questing music.
This says "Beyonce
Bootylicious Dance Mix."